A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Assistant Business Manager, Subject Files, Series 3 FA013
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Assistant Business Manager, Subject Files, Series 3
1905-1958
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
Flinn, Waldo R.
Rockefeller University
Flexner, Simon
Barus, Maxwell
Greene, Jerome D.
James, Henry, Jr.
Cogger, John W.
Smith, Edric Brooks
Brown, Wade H.
Bronk, Detlev W. (Detlev Wulf), 1897-1975
Pearce, Louise, b. 1886
Norris, James U.
Jacobs, Walter A. (Walter Abraham), 1883-1967
FA013
14.08 Cubic Feet 32 document cases
File Plan
Former Classification: I 212-3
Arrangement note
The Assistant Business Manager records are arranged in multiple series:
Series 2: Correspondence
Series 3: Subject Files
Series 5: Social Service Records
Conditions Governing Access
Series 3: Limited access. Personnel files and employee records are restricted due to personal confidential information and salary information.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be closed to research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be closed to researchers at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/Head of Reference.
Other Finding Aids
FA806 Rockefeller University records, Assistant Business Manager, Correspondence, Series 2
FA807 Rockefeller University records, Assistant Business Manager, Social Service records, Personnel, Series 5
Vivisection; Patent medicines; Tryparsamide; Civil defense; Wages -- Accounting; Health insurance; Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research; Flinn, Waldo R.; Rockefeller University; Flexner, Simon; Barus, Maxwell; Greene, Jerome D.; James, Henry, Jr.; Cogger, John W.; Smith, Edric Brooks; Brown, Wade H.; Bronk, Detlev W. (Detlev Wulf), 1897-1975; Pearce, Louise, b. 1886; Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research. War Demonstration Hospital; Merck & Co; Norris, James U.; Jacobs, Walter A. (Walter Abraham), 1883-1967
- Subject Files, 1905-1958, n.d.; 3; 14.08 Cubic Feet 32 boxes
  Arrangement
  Organized into 7 subseries:
  1a. Correspondence 1. Civil Defense 2. John W. Cogger - Employee Records 3. Waldo R. Flinn - Personnel Files 4. Insurance 5. Miscellaneous 6. Edric B. Smith - Subject Files
  Arranged alphabetically by subject, and then alphabetically within each subject.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Limited access. Personnel files and employee records are restricted from scholarly access due to personal confidential material and salary information.
  - Correspondence, 1913-1941; 1a; 3 Cubic Feet
    Arranged alphabetically by subject.
    Scope and Contents
    File of correspondence dealing with the areas of responsibility of the assistant business manager.
    - Employees, 1917-1941 (Box 1)
      Material from early years added to file. Much of the correspondence deals with sick leaves.
    - Equipment, 1913-1928 (Box 1)
      Johnson Service Co. 1915-1928. Thermostats and temperature control for animal house, greenhouse, and laboratory. Manning, Maxwell, & Moore. 1915-1916. Machine shop tools Meyer Sniffen Co. 1915-1921. Basins and faucets. Standard Scientific Co. 1914-1916. Imported glassware and Customs questions. Oscar Stolp. Animal cages. Arthur H. Thomas Co. Electric heating. Roger Williams. Automatic control for incubator heating.
    - Exhibits, 1913-1925 (Box 1)
      1913-1914 Correspondence on exhibit in Lyons 1921-1925 Exhibit for Pasteur Centenary; correspondence, photographs, and programs. Includes program for exhibit at New York Academy of Medicine.
    - Insurance, 1913-1928 (Box 2)
      Consists primarily of correspondence with Merchants Fire Assurance Corp. dealing with coverage on both NYC and Princeton laboratories and some claims.
    - I-On-A-Co, 1925-1927, June 1948 (Box 2)
      Correspondence with T.M. Debevoise, Better Business Bureau, and inquirers dealing with Gaylord Wilshire's useof the Institute name in medical advertising.
    - International Instrument Company, 1913-1914 (Box 2)
      Primarily material regarding purchase and installation of centrafuge. Includes drawings and blueprints.
    - Invitations, 1913-1931 (Box 2)
      Acceptances and regrets for varied functions.
    - Jarvis Engineering, 1915-1923 (Box 3)
    - Kauffman, Fritz, 1924-1927 (Box 3)
      Correspondence with wish to work at RIMR under RF grant.
    - Personnel, 1912-1916 (Box 3)
      1912-1913 Womens Educational and Industrial Union 1913-1916 Primarily correspondence with Intercollegiate Bureau of Occupations, N.Y. for placement of educated women. Includes 1st report. See also Employees.
    - Visitors, 1913-1926 (Box 3)
      Correspondence dealing with arrangements for visitors to RIMR including announcements of some lectures.
    - Zonite, 1922-1924 (Box 3)
      Correspondence dealing with implication of RIMR involvement in preparation. Misleading advertising of Carrel-Dakin solution.
  - Civil Defense, 1941-1957; 1; 1.76 Cubic Feet 4 boxes
    Arranged alphabetically.
    Includes correspondence and minutes; also includes brochures, enrollment cards, memos, notes, and reports.
    Subjects include the cooperative civil defense program between New York Hospital and the RIMR and a manual of civil defense.
    - Air Raid Preparations, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      File Plan
      Former Classification: I 212.3, Box 4
    - Air Raid Preparations, 1951-1955 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - American Red Cross, 1951-1954 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Assignment Lists, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Bulletins - New York Hospital, 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Code List, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Committee Meetings, 1951-1953 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Committees: Civil Defense Meetings (RIMR), 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Committees: General Committee on Civil Defense - New York Hospital, 1950-1953 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1951-1957 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Department of Hospitals: City of New York, 1950-1953 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Department of Hospitals: City of New York, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Enrollment Cards I, 1950-1957 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Enrollment Cards II, 1950-1957 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Fire Control Program, 1950-1954 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - First Aid, 1951-1956 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - First Aid Classes, 1951-1954 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - General Material, 1950-1952 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - General Material, 1952-1958 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Manual of Civil Defense - Draft, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Manual of Civil Defense I, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Manual of Civil Defense II, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Manual of Civil Defense III, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Manual of Civil Defense IV, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Memos: Flinn, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Memos: Gasser, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Memos: General, 1951-1957 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Memos: Smith, 1951-1953 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Office of Civil Defense, 1950-1954 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Princeton: Data on Sale of Institute Property, 1947-1950 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Subcommittees: Basic Plans - New York Hospital, 1950-1951 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Subcommittees: Casualty - New York Hospital, 1950-1951 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Subcommittees: Evacuation and Admitting - New York Hospital, 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Subcommittees: Miscellaneous - New York Hospital, 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Subcommittees: Nursing - New York Hospital, 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Subcommittees: Professional Care and Training - New York Hospital, 1951-1953 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Subcommittees: Radioactivity - New York Hospital, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Subcommittees: Records, Communications, and Supplies - New York Hospital, 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Subcommittees: Security and Plant Operations - New York Hospital, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Subcommittees: Volunteer Recruitment and Assignment - New York Hospital, 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Subversive Organizations, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - John W. Cogger - Employee Records, ca. 1955-1958; 2; 1.32 Cubic Feet 3 boxes
    Biographical / Historical
    John W. Cogger was appointed Personnel Supervisor in 1955 when Waldo R. Flinn was promoted to Business Manager. Cogger handled the records of non-academic personnel.
    Related Materials
    FA137 Rockefeller University records, Business Manager, Subject Files, Boxes 41.
    See Archivist for identification of related materials and further assistance.
    Arranged alphabetically by employee's last name.
    Includes applications, correspondence (including letters of recommendation and reference inquiries), and payroll information.
    Personnel files and employee records are restricted from scholarly access due to personal confidential material and salary information.
    - A, 1955-1958 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - B-BL, 1955-1958 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - BO-BZ, 1955-1958 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - C-CL, 1955-1958 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - CO-CZ, 1955-1958 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - D, 1955-1958 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - E, 1955-1958 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - F, 1955-1958 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - G, 1955-1958 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - H, 1955-1958 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - I, 1955-1958 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - J, 1955-1958 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - K, 1955-1958 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - L, 1955-1958 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - M-MA, 1955-1958 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - ME-MZ, 1955-1958 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - N, 1955-1958 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - O, 1955-1958 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - P-Q, 1955-1958 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - R, 1955-1958 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - S-SL, 1955-1958 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - SM-SZ, 1955-1958 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - W-Z, 1955-1958 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Waldo R. Flinn - Personnel Files, 1930-1956; 3; 3.96 Cubic Feet 9 boxes
    See also: FA137 Rockefeller University records, Business Manager, Subject Files, Boxes 10 and 25.
    Waldo R. Flinn was Assistant Business Manager from 1927-1955, at which time he was promoted to Business Manager. He held this post until his retirement in 1965. During the time he served as Assistant Business Manager, he had the responsibility of handling the records of non-academic personnel.
    Includes correspondence(including letters of recommendation and reference inquiries); also includes applications.
    - A-AL, 1930-1956 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - B-BE, 1930-1956 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - BF-BO, 1930-1956 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - BP-BR, 1930-1956 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - BU-BZ, 1930-1956 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - C-CA, 1930-1956 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - CE-CL, 1930-1956 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - CO, 1930-1956 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - CR-CZ, 1930-1956 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - D-DE, 1930-1956 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - DI-DONN, 1930-1956 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - DONNE-DZ, 1930-1956 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - E, 1930-1956 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - F-FL, 1930-1956 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - FO-FZ, 1930-1956 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - G-GF, 1930-1956 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - GI-GO, 1930-1956 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - GR-GZ, 1930-1956 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - H-HAP, 1930-1956 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - HAR-HAZ, 1930-1956 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - HE-HI, 1930-1956 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - HO-HZ, 1930-1956 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - I, 1930-1956 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - J-JE, 1930-1956 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - JO-JZ, 1930-1956 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - K-KE, 1930-1956 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - KI-KOI, 1930-1956 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - KOL-KZ, 1930-1956 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - L-LA, 1930-1956 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - LE, 1930-1956 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - LI-LON, 1930-1956 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - LOP-LZ, 1930-1956 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - M-MACH, 1930-1956 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - MACI-MACT, 1930-1956 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - MAG-MAZ, 1930-1956 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - ME-MI, 1930-1956 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - MO, 1930-1956 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - MU-MZ, 1930-1956 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - N, 1930-1956 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - O, 1930-1956 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - P-PA, 1930-1956 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - PE-PI, 1930-1956 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - PL-PZ, 1930-1956 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Q, 1930-1956 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - R-RE, 1930-1956 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - RH-ROD, 1930-1956 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - ROG-RZ, 1930-1956 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - S-SCHE, 1930-1956 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - SCHI-SE, 1930-1956 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - SH-SL, 1930-1956 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - SM-SO, 1930-1956 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - SP-STA, 1930-1956 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - STE-SZ, 1930-1956 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - T-TH, 1930-1956 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - TI-V, 1930-1956 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - W-WH, 1930-1956 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - WI-Z, 1930-1956 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Insurance, 1939-1958; 4; 3.52 Cubic Feet 8 boxes
    Includes correspondence and forms; also includes contracts and notes. Subjects include annuities, CREF, death claims, retirement insurance, and TIAA.
    - Death Claims - A, 1939-1957 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Death Claims - B, 1939-1957 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Death Claims - C, 1939-1957 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Death Claims - D, 1939-1957 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Death Claims - F, 1939-1957 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Death Claims - H-I, 1939-1957 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Death Claims - K, 1939-1957 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Death Claims - L, 1939-1957 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Death Claims - M, 1939-1957 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Death Claims - O, 1939-1957 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Death Claims - P, 1939-1957 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Death Claims - R, 1939-1957 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Death Claims - S, 1939-1957 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Death Claims - T, 1939-1957 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Death Claims - V-W, 1939-1957 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Annuities, 1939-1947 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Annuities, 1948-1957 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Annuity Contracts, 1942-1952 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Cases re Evidence of Age: Normal, 1939 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Cases re Evidence of Age: Special, 1939 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Changes in Beneficiaries (Annuities): A-L, 1939-1949 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Changes in Beneficiaries (Annuities): M-Z, 1939-1949 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Changes in Contracts I, 1939 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Changes in Contracts II, 1939 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1937-1939 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - CREF Material, 1952-1956 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Dates of Birth Cleared for Employees, 1939 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Index: Contracts Assigned (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Index: Contracts Repurchased (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Index: Contracts Past Service Contract Numbers (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Institute Procedures I, 1926-1943 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Institute Procedures II, 1926-1943 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Institute Procedures III, 1926-1943 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Institute Procedures IV, 1926-1943 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Pay Increases, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Plans: Employee Benefit Plan Summary for TIAA, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Plans: Retiring Allowance Plan Notes, 1953-1954 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Rice Sheets, 1938-1939 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Sick Leaves, 1934-1935, 1938-1944 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Sick Leaves, 1945-1949 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Supplements, 1951-1958 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - TIAA Computation of Past Contracts, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - TIAA Material, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Transfers to RIMR Plan, 1945-1946 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Retirement and Group Life Deduction Forms: A, 1939-1958 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Retirement and Group Life Deduction Forms: B-BL, 1939-1958 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Retirement and Group Life Deduction Forms: BO-BZ, 1939-1958 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Retirement and Group Life Deduction Forms: C-CL, 1939-1958 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Retirement and Group Life Deduction Forms: CO-CZ, 1939-1958 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Retirement and Group Life Deduction Forms: D, 1939-1958 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Retirement and Group Life Deduction Forms: E, 1939-1958 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Retirement and Group Life Deduction Forms: F, 1939-1958 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Retirement and Group Life Deduction Forms: G, 1939-1958 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Retirement and Group Life Deduction Forms: H-HI, 1939-1958 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Retirement and Group Life Deduction Forms: HO-HZ, 1939-1958 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Retirement and Group Life Deduction Forms: I-J, 1939-1958 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Retirement and Group Life Deduction Forms: K, 1939-1958 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Retirement and Group Life Deduction Forms: L, 1939-1958 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Retirement and Group Life Deduction Forms: M-MA, 1939-1958 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Retirement and Group Life Deduction Forms: ME-MZ, 1939-1958 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Retirement and Group Life Deduction Forms: N-O, 1939-1958 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Retirement and Group Life Deduction Forms: P-Q, 1939-1958 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Retirement and Group Life Deduction Forms: R, 1939-1958 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Retirement and Group Life Deduction Forms: S-SI, 1939-1958 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Retirement and Group Life Deduction Forms: SJ-SZ, 1939-1958 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Retirement and Group Life Deduction Forms: T, 1939-1958 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Retirement and Group Life Deduction Forms: U-V, 1939-1958 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Retirement and Group Life Deduction Forms: W, 1939-1958 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Retirement and Group Life Deduction Forms: X-Z, 1939-1958 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous, 1925-1955; 5; 0.44 Cubic Feet 1 box
    Includes correspondence, notes, and pamphlets. Subjects include apartments leased by the Institute; background material for the Descriptive Pamphlet; New Zealand white rabbits; and tryparsamide.
    - Apartments Leased by Institute I, 1940-1955 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Apartments Leased by Institute II, 1940-1955 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Apartments Leased by Institute III, 1940-1955 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Descriptive Pamphlet Material, 1934 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Descriptive Pamphlet Material, 1937-1938 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Descriptive Pamphlet Material I, 1944-1946 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Descriptive Pamphlet Material II, 1944-1946 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - New Zealand White Rabbits, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Tryparsamide Literature, 1925-1934 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Edric B. Smith-Subject Files, 1905-1920; 6; 1.76 Cubic Feet 4 boxes
    Edric B. SMith was appointed to the Institute in 1913 as Assistant Business Manager. In 1918 he was appointed Acting Business Manager and then Business Manager in 1920, a post he held until his retirement in 1955. These files include the records of James U. Norris, Jerome D. Greene, and Henry James, Jr. (Smith's predecessors as Business/General Manager).
    Includes correspondence and reports; also includes articles, building plans, contracts, notes, pamphlets, and statistics. Correspondents include Simon Flexner, Jerome D. Greene, Henry James Jr., and James U. Norris. Subjects include anti-vivisectionism, budgets, buildings, and the War Demonstration Hospital. Some personal records of Smith are also included.
    - American Society of Mechanical Engineers, 1918-1920 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Animal Cages, 1915 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Animal House Assignments, 1915 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Anti-Vivisection, 1908-1914 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Applications for Positions, 1914 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Budget Materials, 1909-1911 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Budget Materials, 1911-1913 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Budget Materials, 1913-1914 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Budget Materials, 1915-1916 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Budget Materials, 1916-1917 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Budget Materials & War Demonstration Hospital, 1917-1918 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Budget Materials, 1917-1918 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Budget Materials, 1918-1919 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Buildings - Committee Notes, 1915-1916 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Buildings - Maintenance and Alterations, 1913-1915 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, 1915 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Coal Purchasing, 1909, 1914 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Construction - Reports on New, 1914 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Director's Meetings, 1918 Spring (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Director's Meetings, 1918 Fall (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Director's Meetings, 1919 January (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Dogs - Purchasing, 1914 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Draft Registration, 1918 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Electrical Work (Hixon Elec. Co.), 1915 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Estimates - Misc - Norris, 1910 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Farm Buildings, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Flexner, Simon, 1914-1919 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Flooring, 1913 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Harvard Engineering Soicety of New York, 1916-1918 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Heating and Ventilating Contracts, 1914-1915 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - James, Henry, 1912-1916 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - James, Henry, 1917-1918, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Janitors Supplies, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Lamp Contract, 1914 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - New Building, 1912-1914 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Norris, J./Greene, J.D., 1910-1912 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Painting and Painters, 1913-1915 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1913-1917 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1918-1920 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Police Department, 1916 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Power Plant Papers, 1913-1914 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Princeton Notes, 1916 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Public Costs, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Reception, 1914 November 20 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Scientific Staff, 1910 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Steam Flow Meters, 1913 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Sterilizer, 1912-1915 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Treasurer's Report, 1918 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Vacation Schedules, 1915 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Ventilation, 1905-1907 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Wages, 1918 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - War Deomstration Hospital and War Activities, 1918-1919 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Zoo Buildings, 1913 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Extracts from Payroll Volumes, 1906-1911 (Box 32, Folder 18)